hi
today we are going to start an easy but long task
making a star gate in GTNH
this pack is known for being rather easy
so we are going to play in hardcore
in the rare eventuality that we will die
all we will have to do is load a backup
the first thing we shall do is to dispose of that book
since books are boring
and we do not have free slots in our inventory
we also do not have time for reading it
we can now proceed into looking at a place with grass green enough
and then start digging our basement
now that we have found green grass
we can start to collect the resources for a bed
this pack is not as bad as vanilla Minecraft
but it is still not realistic enough
the bed only requires some wool and some wood
there is no need for screws, glue or anything to hold it together
probably it is held in place with magic
anyways let's start gathering the required resources before the night arrives
now that we have a bed we can make some tools
that way, we can gather materials more quickly
and we can also dig our basement into Hard Rock
we must not forget that this pack also has some quests
let's give them a look
yeah I'm not reading that stuff
we shall only complete the required tasks that will lead us to the star gate nothing more
after a long day of work
we shall have a nice sleep while watching the sunset
we will then have breakfast with an apple
so that the doctors will stay away
now that we have a shelter and some resources
we can start looking into the tasks given us by the gods of the book
since we did not follow it until now
we are rewarded with having to craft again half of the stuff we already did
we shall now start farming some food
we will be using it as a sacrifice to the gods of the book
since we are playing in hardcore mode
we are going to have a vegetarian diet
that way
zombies and skeletons won't attack us
as they will see us as an already dead entity
it seems that the gods of the book won't like our diet
they are asking us to make a sword
and slay some poor animals
with no apparent reason
we do not have the power for opposing the gods
so we shall do as they say
as asked by the gods
we shall slay six pigs and six sheeps
after a long day of fighting
all we need is a well deserved night of sleep
to forget about all the cruelty the gods made us do
or maybe not
we shall spend the night thinking about the cruelty we did when we fist arrived
we shouldn't have thrown away the sacred book we were given during the creation of this world
we shall spend the rest of the night digging a better basement
it appears that the gods accepted our regrets
as you can see from the gods message
it is now time to emerge back to the surface
and touch some grass
it appears that the gods gifted us with the blessing of some string
we shall not forget about this incredible gift we just received
we can now go gather some more of the resources required in our path to the Star Gate
like some wood and some gravel
we must be careful not to let any log float in the air
or the gods may get mad at us again
we might also start making a nice looking house above our basement
so that people won't look too badly at us
and after a long day of work we can finally sleep
today we are going to explore this beautiful world given us by the gods of the book
actually we are looking for some useful resources
that might helps us in our mission of making a star gate
we have found some source of rubber and also some clay while on the way
after all of that exploration
we shall sleep
and oh god no
why
maybe that is a sign that we shall work more on our basement
we must make it look as if a creeper exploded inside it
it is now getting too dark in here
our only saviour could be our old friend, NEI
let's ask him how to make glowing sticks
we are lucky we can use the resin we found earlier with string we were given by the gods
to make the holy glowing sticks
they are holy because they never burn out
we shall now take a few seconds
to appreciate how nice our basement looks
no creepers exploded in here
however
a creeper lives here
and the gods rewarded us with more string
now we can gather some clay
we can set up the start of our farm
where we will be farming cotton and wheat
that way, we will be able to produce our own string
with out having to rely on the gifts from the gods
we can use wheat for our future cow farm
and also to make food for us
and with the newly acquired food and light source
we can go gather some materials underground
so that we can start building our industry
now that we have all of these resources
I think it is a good time to have some resting sleep
and then start building our factory of pollution
now it's time to start
wait
where am I is this a dream
it looks like what I was planning to do
it has to be an illustrative dream
where I can explain my plans
so be it
here we will have a smeltery
for making bronze tier tools and the first molds
and next to it we have the coke ovens for making creosote oil
now I think we should go outside to touch some grass
and plan our automated farm
wait this tree looks kinda sus
apparently Santa gifted us with some coal
but it looks like this coal kinda went bad
I hope it's still good enough for our boilers
wait, wtf did just happen
it should have not destroyed the message
now let's heat up this spoiled coal which almost turned bad into shiny trash
we might be able to revert it back into burnable coal by heating it up
but that could require one whole bucket of creosote oil
please god
make it revert back to burnable coal
okay I do not know if that worked as it should have
but it looks like we can still burn that stuff
now
here we have a boiler
it burns coal to produce steam
great it accepted our rotten coal
now we have to give it some water
let's go fetch it
we do not want to use that murky water from a swamp
we shall go gather clean water form a river
now that the boiler have heated up a bit
we can finally add the water
so that we will get instantly steam
wait what happened
why is it all dark
what kind of dream is that
am I finally waking up
and now what is this place
it looks like we have found a way to go to heaven
oh, wow
so it looks like heaven is powered by nukes
but it looks like this is not properly set it up
let me help you God
if we stack the cells closer
the output should be greater
and we should also obtain a higher efficiency
like that
now we have to turn off this infernal device
wait
what is that music
where is it coming from
and how can you actually die in heaven
and now what happens
guys I have a plan B
we just reload a backup from before we had the weird dream
let's do it
OK
I can't see our Star Gate mission
we can either go into a generic world
or, yeah let's go with the mission B
now we have to figure a way out of this ice kite thing
this looks like a control room
here
there are some levers that we shall randomly shuffle
that way, God will be mad at us and send us back to our basement
and what is that weird looking pipe
what just passed inside it
whatever
okay
it looks like nothing really happened this time
let's look around for an universe traveling machine
that looks like it
let's give it a try
hey
it worked
I'm back in the world of my dreams
silly God
okay
before this pray pod thing, I want to check if Santa's coal is still there
that's not funny though
how do we power our boilers now
shall we be bad or good kids to receive some coal next year
let's try with some pray
how does that works
the instructions seems pretty hard
please give me some steam
okay
double that
but how do we produce steam
can we have a God blessed boiler
please help me God
okay
is this a boilers that runs on holy water and God's light?
please help me
enlighten me
maybe this time the answer is not above us but below us
wait what what happened okay
this is not funny anymore
is this a dream
an isekai
or what I have an idea
we take this magic wand
and start building a nice looking steam setup using magic
let's do it
and here we go
嗨！
今天我们要开始一项简单却漫长的任务
在GTNH中制作星门
这个包以极低的难度闻名
所以让我们用极限模式玩吧
因为我们有极低的概率嗝屁
所以要做的就是加载备份
我们要做的第一件事就是处理掉那本书
因为看书很无聊
而且背包也没有空闲位置留给它
时间也不允许我们这么做
现在可以继续找一个绿草茵茵的地方了
然后开始挖出地下室
既然我们找到了一片草地
可以开始找东西来做床了
这包比原版好一点
但还是不够现实
床只需要一些羊毛和木头
不需要螺丝、胶水或任何东西来将其固定在一起
可能是用魔法固定的
无论如何，让我们在夜晚到来之前开始收集所需的资源
有了床，我们可以做些工具
可以更快地收集材料
我们把地下室挖到石头层
别忘了这个包还有一些任务
让我们看看
当然，我不会读它
我们只完成星门路上的必要任务
经过一整天的工作
我们一边看着日落一边入睡
然后早餐吃个苹果
医生远离我
我们有了避难所和资源
可以开始研究书中的神交给我们的任务
由于现在我们才开始跟进进度
我们必须再做一次大半我们做过的东西
我们现在先种点吃的
用它们来祭祀书中的神
既然我们在玩极限模式
我们要吃素了
这样的话
僵尸和骷髅将不会攻击我们
因为他们会把我们视为一个已经死亡的实体
看来书中的神不会喜欢我们的饮食
祂要我们做一把剑
杀死一些可怜的动物
原因成谜
我们没有对抗神明的力量
所以我们就照祂说的做
应诸神之命
我们要杀六头猪与六头羊
经过一整天的战斗
我们最需要的就是睡上一觉奖励自己
忘记上帝让我们做的所有残忍的事
也可能忘不了
我们将整晚思考我们拳头落下所造成的残忍
我们不应该扔掉在创造此世界获得的圣书
我们用剩下的时间挖一个更好的地下室
看来诸神接受了我们的歉意
正如你从神的信息中看到的
是时候回到地表
透一透气
看来诸神赐予了我们一些蛛丝
我们不会忘记刚刚收到的这份不可思议的礼物
我们现在可以去收集更多通往星门所需的资源了
像一些木头和一些燧石
我们必须小心不要让木头浮在空中
否则众神又要生我们的气了
我们也可以开始在地下室上面建一栋漂亮的房子
别人就不会鄙视我们了
经过一整天的工作，我们终于可以睡觉了
今天我们要探索书中诸神赋予我们的美丽世界
实际上我们正在寻找一些有用的资源
也许能帮助我们完成建造星门的任务
我们在路上找到了一些橡胶和粘土的来源
在所有的探索之后
我们要睡觉了
哦，上帝，不
为什么
这应该昭示了我们应该多装修一下地下室
我们必须让它看起来像一只苦力怕在里面爆炸了
现在这里太暗了
我们唯一的救世主可能是我们的老朋友NEI
问问他怎么做发光棒
我们很幸运，我们可以将之前找到的树脂
与神给我们的蛛丝一起使用
制作神圣发光的棍子
它们是神圣的，因为永远不会燃烧殆尽
让我们花几秒钟来欣赏我们的地下室有多漂亮
没有苦力怕在这爆炸过
然而
这里住着一只苦力怕
众神奖励我们更多的蛛丝
现在我们可以收集一些粘土
建起我们的农村
我们将在那里种植棉花和小麦
这样可以自给自足线
不需要依靠神的恩赐
小麦能用在未来的奶牛圈建设里
也可以用来当食物
有了新获得的食物和光源
我们可以去地下收集一些材料
这样我们就可以开始建设我们的工业
现在我们有了所有这些资源
我想现在是休息的好时机
然后开始建造污染工厂
现在是时候开始
补兑
我在哪里？这是一场梦吗？
这看上去就是我的基地计划
这肯定是一个梦
用来解释我计划的梦
那就这样吧
在这里我们将有一个冶炼厂
用于制作青铜工具和第一批模具
旁边是焦炉，用来制造杂酚油
现在我想我们应该出去碰些草
并规划我们的自动化农场
等等，这棵树有点可疑
显然圣诞老人给了我们一些煤
但看起来这煤有点劣质了
我希望它对我们的锅炉来说仍然足够好
等等，刚刚发生了什么？
它不应该破坏告示牌
现在让我们把这些几乎变质成闪亮垃圾的煤加热
我们也许可以通过加热把它还原成可燃煤
但那可能需要一整桶杂酚油
拜托上帝
变回可燃煤
好吧，我不知道这是否有效
但看起来我们还是可以烧掉那些东西
现在
这里有一个锅炉
它燃烧煤炭产生蒸汽
太好了，它接受了我们的烂煤
现在我们得给它一些水
让我们去取一些
我们不想用沼泽里的浑水
我们要去河里收集干净的水
现在锅炉有点温度了
终于可以加水了
这样我们就会立即得到蒸汽
等等怎么回事
怎么都黑了
这是什么鬼梦
我终于醒来了吗
现在我们在哪
看来我们找到了通往天堂的路
噢，哇
所以看起来天堂是核驱动的
但看起来这没有正确设置
让我帮助你，上帝
如果我们把单元堆得更近
输出应该更高
效率也会更高
像那样
现在我们得关掉这个该死的装置
等等
那是什么音乐
它从哪里传来？
一个人怎么可能会死在天堂里？
现在会发生什么？
伙计们我有个B计划
我们只要重新加载做这个奇怪的梦之前的备份
让我们开始吧
好的
我看不到我们的星门任务
我们要么进入一个通用的世界
或者，是的，让我们选择方案B
现在我们得想个办法解决这个冰上风筝的事
这里看起来像一个控制室
在这里
我们去随机打乱一下这些个拉杆
那样的话上帝会生我们的气而把我们送回地下室
那个看起来很奇怪的管子是什么？
什么东西刚刚穿过？
随便了
好吧
看起来这次什么都没发生
让我们四处寻找宇宙旅行机器
看起来是这个
让我们试一试
嘿
它起作用了
我回到了我梦中的世界
傻上帝
好吧
在祈求资源之前，我想检查一下圣诞老人的煤是否还在那里
这一点也不好笑
我们现在如何为锅炉供电？
明年该变坏呢？还是成为好孩子再获得些煤
让我们再祈求一下
这是怎么回事？
给的指示太难了
请给我一些蒸汽
好吧
再来一个
但是我们如何产生蒸汽呢？
我们能有一个上帝保佑的锅炉吗？
请帮帮我上帝
好吧
这是一个用圣水和上帝之光运行的锅炉吗？
请帮帮我
开导我
也许这次答案不在我们上面而是在下面
等等发生了什么事
这一点都不好笑了
这是梦吗
一个异世界
或者我有个主意
我们拿着这根魔杖
开始用魔法建造一个漂亮的蒸汽装置
让我们开始吧
完事
（我只是在开玩笑捏
嘻嘻
——上帝）
（还没到圣诞节呢
笑死）
（祈祷
然后
跳）
（我又在开玩笑了
嘻嘻
——上帝）
（去看《想要成为影之实力者！》）
（试试许愿池→）
（不管怎么说
你的祈愿已经
被实现了）